[
  {
    "url": "https://www.iitkgp.ac.in",
    "title": "indian institute technology",
    "category": "Research",
    "keywords": [
      "indian",
      "students",
      "faculty",
      "staff",
      "visitors",
      "affairs",
      "jobs",
      "academics",
      "admissions",
      "research"
    ],
    "text": "indian institute technology kharagpur iit kgp administration students faculty staff visitors outreach alumni affairs jobs english academics admissions research industry",
    "named_entities": {
      "ORG": "krishi machinery",
      "NORP": "german",
      "DATE": "year",
      "PRODUCT": "geo",
      "PERSON": "llm mcp",
      "CARDINAL": "seven",
      "GPE": "ramachandran"
    }
  },
  {
    "url": "https://www.iitkgp.ac.in",
    "title": "indian institute technology",
    "category": "Research",
    "keywords": [
      "indian",
      "students",
      "faculty",
      "staff",
      "visitors",
      "affairs",
      "jobs",
      "academics",
      "admissions",
      "research"
    ],
    "text": "indian institute technology kharagpur iit kgp administration students faculty staff visitors outreach alumni affairs jobs english academics admissions research industry",
    "named_entities": {
      "ORG": "krishi machinery",
      "NORP": "german",
      "DATE": "year",
      "PRODUCT": "geo",
      "PERSON": "llm mcp",
      "CARDINAL": "seven",
      "GPE": "ramachandran"
    }
  },
  {
    "url": "https://www.iitkgp.ac.in",
    "title": "indian institute technology",
    "category": "Research",
    "keywords": [
      "indian",
      "students",
      "faculty",
      "staff",
      "visitors",
      "affairs",
      "jobs",
      "academics",
      "admissions",
      "research"
    ],
    "text": "indian institute technology kharagpur iit kgp administration students faculty staff visitors outreach alumni affairs jobs english academics admissions research industry",
    "named_entities": {
      "ORG": "krishi machinery",
      "NORP": "german",
      "DATE": "year",
      "PRODUCT": "geo",
      "PERSON": "llm mcp",
      "CARDINAL": "seven",
      "GPE": "ramachandran"
    }
  },
  {
    "url": "https://www.iitkgp.ac.in",
    "title": "indian institute technology",
    "category": "Research",
    "keywords": [
      "indian",
      "students",
      "faculty",
      "staff",
      "visitors",
      "affairs",
      "jobs",
      "academics",
      "admissions",
      "research"
    ],
    "text": "indian institute technology kharagpur iit kgp administration students faculty staff visitors outreach alumni affairs jobs english academics admissions research industry"
  }
  
]